[Music]
[Música]
I have a different way of thinking and no Look,
yo tengo otra forma de pensar y no Mira
the other day I was talking to
yo el otro día estaba hablando con
someone from television and I told him that
alguien de la televisión y le dije que
lately the television programs
últimamente los programas de televisión
where there was this type of folklore were
donde estaba este tipo de folklore era
a factory of starving people and it's
una fábrica de muertos de hambre y es
true it is a factory of
verdad es una fábrica de muertos de
starving people because many of them are
hambre porque muchos de ellos son unos
starving people
muertos de hambre en busca de
looking for something to talk about
en busca de hacer algo que se hable de
them so that someone is worth 4000 pieces
ellos para que alguien es de 4000gajas
worth
vale
a person that I think lives
una persona de las que pienso que vive
this way well it's that person that you
de esta forma pues es esa persona que
just said no because in this mess that there has been of let's see
acabáis de decir no porque en el lío
I
este que ha habido de vamos a ver yo
just think that you Elías with a turkey
solo pensar que te Elías con un pavo
okay he's married that he's going to give something to
vale que está casado que ya va a dar que
talk about and you get involved at a party of the
hablar y te lías en una fiesta de la
production company it's like getting involved in the set of
productora es como liarte en el plato de
Sálvame So that's because you
sálvame Entonces eso es porque tú
really want it to be known you want it to be
realmente quieres que se sepa quieres
said and you want to make some friends
que se diga y Quieres ganar alguna amiga
from that because maybe you are so boring that you
de eso porque igual eres tan cascosa que
need those things to put a
necesitas esas cosas para llevarte un
piece of bread in your mouth you understand That is
cacho pan a la boca me entiendes Ese es
the big problem with many now on
el gran problema de muchos ahora en
television that they become some
televisión que se convierten en unos
boring people eh they go on telling  movies And mind you,
cascosos eh van contando películas Y ojo
with this I'm not trying to say that Jorge
yo con esto no intento decir que Jorge
Jorge is a Manzanillo who has arrived
Jorge es un Manzanillo que ha llegado
there on television,
allá a la televisión
which means
que significa
a guy who has arrived on TV like
un tío que ha llegado a la tele en plan
I don't know what I am.
Yo qué sé soy
I'm the king of fried
yo soy aquí el rey del pollo frito que
chicken here, I'm very good and on TV there are survivors who will beat up whoever they can to make some money And that was yesterday with the with the let's see, no disrespect to anyone who works in TV, but a little like full, not
la tele pero un poco como llenas no en
like if there's a piece of meat there's
plan si hay un cacho de carne que
only one for 20, you have to
solamente hay uno para 20 hay que hay
be the one who beats up the most, the one who
que ser el que más machaque el que más
bites the most so that
muerda para que
also, I'll tell you one thing, what
además te digo una cosa lo que ha hecho
this girl has done, I think the one who
esta chica que yo creo que la que lo ha
leaked it is her, she did it with another time,
filtrado es ella lo hizo con otra vez
but well, she leaked it because she knows
pero bueno lo ha filtrado ya porque sabe
that it was being seen in the production company
que se estaba viendo en la productora
if I'm married and I have four children, it would
si yo estoy casado y tengo cuatro hijos
n't occur to me to get involved with one of them, one of them
no se me ocurre liarme con una unos uno
is definitely a Manzanillo and the other
desde luego es un Manzanillo y la otra
is a tall one who knows how
es una larga que sabe cómo funciona la
TV works What happens is that I brought him there
tele Lo que pasa que lo he traído allí
like Heidi Oh how cool, we're
en plan Heidi Ay qué Guay que somos
all Super Friends here
todos Súper Amigos aquí
and they've given him a hard time
y le han dado para el pelo
[Music]
[Música]
in the bathroom they caught them in the taxi
en el baño los han pilla en el taxi los
[ __ ] the [ __ ] there are more than 20
[__] [__] si es que hay más de 20
videos of the two of them making out and
vídeos de ellos dos enrollándose y
hitting each other inside the party
madreándose dentro de la fiesta
like if I came like a Sandocan
como en plan como venga como sandocán
there bare chested fire
ahí a pecho descubierto fuego
delighted she says I already have enough for
encantada de la vida dice ya tengo para
a year's mortgage
un año de hipoteca
[Laughs]
[Risas]
tell me Pepa
dime [__]
Leo what she says what she says Ivan Alba is
Leo que dice lo que dice Iván Alba está
delighted well if she
encantada de la vida Bueno si se
laughs she's happy then the mother will come out
descojona está feliz luego saldrá la
look after Alma comes the
madre mira después de Alma viene la
mother will come to tell the battles
madre que vendrá a contar las batallas
but they are worse than a pain
pero son más malas que un dolor vendrá
the mother will come to tell some story
la madre a contar alguna película
get angry and all this will derive between
enfadarse y todo esto derivará entre
when the mother opens a set she will get
cuando la madre abren algún plató se
angry with the presenter and all this
enfadará con el presentador y todo esto
we have Alba and the mother for another three
tenemos Alba y la madre para otros tres
years the mother is at war on Twitter the
años la madre está guerra en Twitter la
mother is already looking to get into a
madre ya está buscando entrar a un
reality show
reality
she delighted so eat
ella encantada de la vida así come
hot the trip they have there right
caliente la zancadilla que tienen ahí
now in the complaint that they
ahora mismo en la denuncia que le
filed against the network that the
pusieron a la cadena que le puso la
mother filed a complaint against the network and Jorge
madre una denuncia a la cadena y a Jorge
for this argument they had
por la discusión esta que tuvieron el
last winter on the set and man
invierno pasado en el plató y hombre
I am  Okay, when they do
Yo estoy de acuerdo que cuando hacen
something against you that you consider
algo contra ti que tú consideres que
violates your rights, of course you have to
vulneren tus derechos por supuesto
use the law, but of course if your
Tienes que usar la ley pero claro si tu
livelihood is the network,
medio de vida es la cadena de mandarla
then things get a little complicated, but
pues se complica un poco las cosas pero
I think they sue them to then
yo creo que las demandan para luego
blackmail the network. The thing is that
chantajear a la cadena Lo que pasa que
the plan may not have worked out well, for me
igual no lo ha salido bien el plan a mí
the mother is that I don't like her
la madre es que no me cae bien ni ella
or the mother, logically like a large part of
ni la madre lógico como mucha parte de
the general population because, well,
la gran población porque bueno si es que
besides, there's no need to talk much, you just
además no hace falta hablar mucho solo
have to look back a little at
hay que mirar un poco hacia atrás desde
the history she has with
el historial que tiene con los
athletes with this and that and you don't
deportistas con tal Y con cuál y ya no
need to know more. I found it
te hace falta saber más a mí me ha hecho
very funny today because today she said that
mucha gracia hoy porque hoy ha dicho que
she doesn't get involved in these messes, I made the
a ella no meterse en estos líos pasé
front pages. Sorry, I mean
portadas
because you're on the front page, girl, I
Perdona o sea porque eres portada tía o
mean you are, let's see, but yes,
sea eres vamos a ver pero sí
a program is going to be necessary, look, it goes
un programa lo va a hacer falta mira va
twice a week, it's worth 180 and 180,
dos veces por semana vale 180 y 180
let's put 200 euros to do
vamos a poner 200 euros para hacer el
number 2. Let her earn 600 euros a
número 2 Échale que gane 600 euros al
month, a week 6 by 4 24
mes a la semana 6 por 4 24
2400 bucks with 2400 bucks a child and
2400 pavos con 2400 pavos un hijo y una
a mortgage That I think is huge you
una hipoteca Que creo que tiene enorme
understand me No, he doesn't live in a
me entiendes No no vive en una casa
yellow house Cari What happens is that there are people
amarilla Cari Lo que pasa que hay gente
who forget where they came from for
que se le olvida de dónde salió
a master's degree somewhere talking about
por un máster en algún lado hablando de
exes I mean she she knows on a
los ex O sea ella ella conoce en un
program that entered models that no and
programa que entró de modelos que no y
then she hooked up with an athlete was
luego se lió con un deportista estuvo
married to no first she was with Fonsi
casado con no primero estuvo con Fonsi
had a child then the athlete then
tuvo un hijo luego el deportista luego
there's another athlete and the one from Such as how he
hay otro deportista y el de Tal como
leaks it and tells it well already
como lo filtra y lo cuenta pues ya
as a model
de modelo
The guard
El guardia
Ivan Ivan lives in Madrid was going to continue going
Iván Iván vive en Madrid iba a seguir
out to party because he likes to
saliendo de fiesta porque le gusta de
go out for that handsome young man
salir de fiesta para ese joven guapo
fed up and loud and clear in the discos you
harto y fuerte y claro en las discos se
see many things and many stories no
se ve muchas cosas y muchas historias no
but
pero
what Álvaro I have never seen her
el qué Álvaro yo nunca la he visto por
there I have seen her I coincided with her in
ahí Yo la he visto coincidí con ella en
a debate on Telecinco
un debate de telecinco
in a debate I sometimes I am in the
en un debate yo a veces estoy en los
debates of Big Brother and she was there
debates de gran hermano y estaba ella
when Big Brother was on which was the
cuando estaba gran hermano que fue el
last debate I went to coincide
último debate que fui coincidió
what do you think of Marta López the role she
qué pensáis de Marta López el papel que
is playing in this story because I
está jugando en esta historia porque yo
saw her today  like she gets very
la he visto hoy como que se pone muy
well put but she says no no I haven't
bien puesta pero ella dice no no yo no
put my house as a riding school with a
he puesto mi casa de picadero con un
little yes no let's see a little a
poco sí no a ver un poco
little
un poco
please
por favor
we love Marta both Ivan
a Marta la tenemos cariño tanto Iván
and I
como yo
but I don't like the position I'm going to
pero yo no me gusta la posición me voy a
stay like this but I don't like her position
quedar así pero no me gusta su posición
and today too but well she will know each
y hoy también pero bueno ella sabrá cada
one knows But it's what Ivan was saying
uno sabe Pero es lo que estaba diciendo
against Tell me what most told
Iván contra Cuéntame lo que más contado
what we have been talking about you and I
lo que hemos estado hablando tú y yo
this afternoon
esta tarde
that about Marta
el que de Marta
no no that to me it seems that she has
no no que a mí a mí a mí me parece que
done wrong but I don't want to go into
ha hecho mal pero no quiero entrar ya en
more
más
details it seems terrible to me it seems that
detalles me parece fatal me parece que
in the sense of having I wouldn't have well it's
en el sentido de haber yo no hubiese
terrible if you ask me terrible
bueno es que fatal si me preguntas fatal
What
En qué
if now that I remember they have done it
si ahora que me acuerdo lo han hecho
in front of the whole [ __ ] world
delante de todo el [__] mundo
Then they have done it to you in front of the whole
Entonces te lo han hecho delante de todo
world Marta thought well no it's not that they have
el mundo Marta pensaba bueno no nos es
messed up in front of a
que se han liado delante de una
production company where there are 300 guys who are
productora donde hay 300 tíos que están
editors journalists It's normal that it
en redactores periodistas Es normal que
comes out then well Marta has
salga entonces bueno Marta se ha
taken advantage of the subject a little bit
aprovechado ahí un poquito del tema
all eyes are always involved there's no
siempre están todos los ojos metida no
garlic in Spain that no yes  there is nothing
hay ajo en España que no si no hay algo
that Marta is no longer worth a [ __ ]
que esté Marta ya no vale una [__] de
Yeah yeah but it's that
Sí sí pero es que
I see Apart from what they
yo ahí veo Aparte ya de lo que se han
started talking about on the set and everything else, I
puesto a hablar en el plató y demás no
could already grab onto that man
que ya me se podría agarrar a que hombre
that I work here if they ask me I have to
que yo trabajo aquí si me preguntan
talk, I saw two attitudes that
tengo que hablar yo vi dos actitudes que
call my attention
me llaman la atención
the first is that let's
la primera es
see, I have the habit that
que a ver yo tengo la costumbre de que
when people come to my house
cuando vienen gente a mi casa
I am there with them or rather this thing that
yo estoy ahí con ellos o sea esto de que
Jorge shows up at her house at the wee hours of
Jorge aparece en su casa a las tantas de
the morning and leaves them alone in the living room
la madrugada y los deja solo en el salón
with the fireplace on and she goes to
con la chimenea puesta y ella se va a
see Hey well
ver Oye pues Podrían haber participado
The three of them could have participated and let's see if I had a great time
los tres y a ver si lo he pasado pipa
man let's see I send them to a hotel
hombre a ver yo los mando a un hotel
directly
directamente
Yesterday when you were talking to Marina because
Ayer cuando hablabas con Marina porque
I talk to another person that
yo hablo con otra persona que
Ivan knows is very close friends
Iván sabe que tiene mucha amistad con
with Marta
con Marta
and they told me like that he
y me lo dijeron de aquella manera se
went into his room threw the blanket
metió en su habitación se echó la manta
over him and said there he will sort it out with
por encima y dijo allá se la apaña en
these two because they don't pay attention to me and if they
estos dos porque no me hacen caso y si
have to have sex then have it and if they
tienen que tener sexo que tengan y si se
want to fight as if they want to
quieren pelear como si se la quieren a
see each other there they were both when  they
ver ahí estaban los dos cuando se dieron
realized and it was going down in the drinks
cuenta y se le bajaba en las copitas
the vamer would be how we organize this let's
estaría el vamer como organizamos esto a
see what we say because this is going to get out
ver qué decimos porque esto va a salir
because my mother is going to find out my
porque madre mía se va a enterar mi
wife I imagine her and the other one was
mujer me la imagino y la otra estaba
saying if it gets out let it get out Oh honey
diciendo si sale que salga Ay cariño
this is us both let's see I'm not the one to
estos somos los dos a ver yo no soy la
blame when on other occasions eh
culpable cuando en otras ocasiones eh
When when They've done the same to her it
Cuando cuando A ella le han hecho lo
seems to me that it was that she said that
mismo me parece que fue que dijo que
whenever someone goes out with someone there has to be
siempre que uno salía con alguien tiene
a lady who agrees as a
que haber una señorita que acceda como
lady in a contemptuous tone you know yes yes
señorita en tono despectivo ya sabéis sí
So I want to tell you with all
sí Entonces te quiero decir con todo
this, let's see I'm not taking the blame away from
esto a ver yo no quito la culpa a
anyone because the truth is I don't
ninguno porque es que realmente me da
care
igual
if each half of Spain would have to come out
si cada media España tendría que salir
because he cheats on the other
porque le pone los cuernos a la otra
half of Spain and that would have to come out
media España y tendría que salir eso en
live the whole of Spain was separated
directo estaba España entera separados
there we can't have hypocrisy and besides
ahí no podemos tener hipocresía y además
I'm not going to judge the fact of the
yo tampoco voy a juzgar el hecho de los
cheating No, what I judge is that you
cuernos No yo lo que juzgo es que lo
do it to monetize
haces para monetizar
And what are you doing you screw up the marriage of a
Y qué haces jodes el matrimonio de una
person with four children
persona con cuatro hijos
That seems great to me
Eso me parece padre
he's the guilty one and she because she's the one who
él es el culpable y ella porque ella es
leaks it
la que lo filtra
Hello, what does the other one incite him  Manzanillo has
Hola que le incita el otro Manzanillo
just arrived on TV
acaba de llegar a la tele
and doesn't even know what's on TV and
y no sabe ni lo que hay en la tele y se
thinks that there are two friends there we are
cree que allí son dos amis somos
super friends well no the three of us are at
superámicas bueno no estamos los tres en
Marta's house and they were Super Friends the
casa de Marta y eran Súper Amigos los
friends of death The Three Musketeers
amis de la muerte Los tres mosqueteros
Where is Marta and the other one now
Dónde está Marta y la otra ahora
putting him in the wrong place they were such friends
poniéndole verde eran tan amigas
he would believe that she was going to keep quiet and
él se creería que ella se iba a callar y
that she wasn't going to tell him or that she was going
que ella no lo iba a contar o que lo iba
to take him off he thought it was between friends he
a quitar pensaba que estaba entre amis
continues she was going to keep it a secret
se sigue le iba a guardar secreto
he is between people between hustlers
está entre gente entre buscavidas
one way or another
de una forma de otra
[Music]
[Música]